Guide to the Sol Yurick Manuscripts for Publication TAM.268
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- "Destiny Assorted Papers, miscellaneous but important", undated; 4.0 folders 4 folders (Box 36)
- "The King of Malaputa: A Treatment", undated (Box 37)
- "Some Notes Toward a Sociology of Theoretical Obscurity (A Variation on the Thought of Alvin Gouldner)", undated (Box 37)
- "Joseph", Dec 2, 1989-Dec 29, 1989 (Box 37)
- "A Tentative Outline of the Holocaust Museum and Trial Novel-Play", Jan 16, 1990 (Box 37)
- "Try", Feb 19, 1990 (Box 37)
- "Oedipus Coup", 1989-2003; 9.0 folders 9 folders (Box 37)
- "JB" by Ron Dobson, undated (Box 37)
- "Malaputa", undated (Box 37)
- "The Sacrifice" Dobson/Yurick, 1995-1996, undated; 3.0 folders 3 folders (Box 37)
- "Oedipus Outline, Trial of God, etc.", undated (Box 37)
- "About Joseph", undated (Box 37)
- Opinion letter regarding technology and Marxism, undated (Box 37)
- "This fragment is a double meditation: The first is on finance and the second is on the proposition of Magical Birth", undated (Box 37)
- Fragment on the Relationship Between Capitalism and AIDS, undated (Box 37)
- "Some Theses on Power and Capital as a System of Power", undated (Box 37)
- Untitled Fragment on Jewish Identity, undated (Box 37)
- Untitled Fragment Discussing Marxism and Yurick's Development as an Author, undated (Box 37)
- Untitled Fragment Reflecting on Evolution, Philosophy, and Capitalism, undated (Box 37)
- Untitled Fragment Discussing Cold War Policy, Literature, and Evolution, undated (Box 37)
- Untitled Fragment Discussing Marxism and Education, undated (Box 37)
- "Political and Cultural Economy of Plague, Population and Proximity", undated (Box 37)
- "On Spreadsheets", Dec 2000 (Box 37)
- "Faust", undated (Box 37)
- "Memories in the Context of the End of the Cold War", undated (Box 37)
- "Mater", May 1989 (Box 37)
- Ron Hunnings Interviews with Sol Yurick, Oct 19, 1991, undated (Box 38)
- "Capital/ERG", Sep 4, 1989 (Box 38)
- "A Position Paper of Sorts: The Fate of Social Text in the Context of the Ever-Present Crisis", undated (Box 38)
- "Making: the Realms of Facts vs. the Realm of the Imagination", Feb 11, 1991 (Box 38)
- "Horizon-Tour/Aronowitz", Nov 1, 1993 (Box 38)
- Capithese, undated, Dec 28, 1993; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 38)
- Miscellaneous Personal Notes, undated; 6.0 folders 6 folders and 1 USB drive (Box 38)
- "The Sacrifice" Dobson/Yurick, undated; 3.0 folders 3 folders (Box 38)
- "Dionysus at the Beach" Yurick/Dobson/Quigley, 1987 (Box 38)
- "Suite Vengeance" Yurick/Dobson/Quigley, 1987 (Box 38)
- "Body Parts" Dobson/Yurick, undated (Box 38)
- "Gigaflop" Yurick/Krass, undated (Box 38)
- Various Notes, undated; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 38)
- "The Harvesting", undated; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 38)
- "How the Athenians Planned to Trick Freud and Colonize the Mind of the West and Immortalize Themselves", Aug 1989; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 39)
- "Oedipus", Aug 6, 1989 (Box 39)
- "Oediplay", Aug 5, 1989 (Box 39)
- "On Jews", undated (Box 39)
- "On the Deconstruction of the Jews", 1990; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 39)
- "Welcome to the Holocaust Memnotechuem" or "Try", 1990; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 39)
- "Some notes toward a sociology of theoretical obscurity (A variation on the thought of Alvin Gouldner)", undated (Box 39)
- "On Joseph in Egypt's Model for an Agricultural Revolution", undated (Box 39)
- "Malaputa (Auction)", Mar 16, 1989, undated; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 39)
- "The Auction", Mar 1989; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 39)
- "Oedipus, or The Coup", Feb 1989 (Box 39)
- "Project for a Novel: Within this Wooden O", Jan 30, 1989-Mar 9, 1989 (Box 39)
- "Within this Wooden O", 1989; 9.0 folders 9 folders (Box 39)
- "Oediplay", undated (Box 40)
- "The Mystery of the Inner World", undated (Box 40)
- "Semiotext(e)" (includes "The Great Escape" by Sol Yurick), undated (Box 40)
- Fertig (photocopy of book jacket and Chapters 1-20), 1966; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 40)
- "Within this Wooden O", Dec 8, 1989 (Box 40)
- Outline for "Within this Wooden O", Dec 9, 1989 (Box 40)
- "Ellsburg as Ishmael: Rostow as Ahab", 1971 (Box 40)
- "Ellsburg as Ishmael: Nixon as Ahab", undated (Box 40)
- "Selby: Symbolic Intent and Ideological Resistance or Cocksucking and Revolution", undated (Box 40)
- "The Harvesting", undated; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 40)
- "Once Upon a Time", undated (Box 40)
- "The Political Economy of a Junkie's Death", undated (Box 40)
- "On Making Foreign Policy with your Feet" and "The Black Badge", undated (Box 40)
- "A Short Note on the Burden of Proof" and "Symposium Questionnaire", undated (Box 40)
- "This Age of Gold", undated (Box 40)
- "And a Friend to Sit by Your Side", undated (Box 40)
- "Jackie Marries Onassis: An Epithalamium" (Box 40)
- Reviews, 1966-1970; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 40)
- "Burning the Bank of America", undated; 4.0 folders 4 folders (Box 40)
- Contracts Borchardt, 1968-1985; 5.0 folders 5 folders (Box 40)
- "Within this Wooden O", Nov 28, 1992-Nov 30, 1992 (Box 41)
- "Oedipus, or The Coup, or the CIA Oedipus", Nov 2, 1992-Dec 10, 1992 (Box 41)
- "How the Athenians Planned to Trick Freud and Colonize the Mind of the West and Immortalize Themselves", undated (Box 41)
- "The King of Malaputa", Feb 20, 1991-Apr 10, 1991 (Box 41)
- "Project for a Novel: Within this Wooden O", undated (Box 41)
- Draft of a letter addressed to Stanley and Bill, undated (Box 41)
- "Burning of the Bank of America" (fragment), Jan 4, 1993 (Box 41)
- "The Emergence of the Metastate versus the Politics of Ethno-Nationalist Identity", 1993-1994; 4.0 folders 4 folders (Box 41)
- "The Emergence of the Metastate, the Politics of Ethno-Nationalist Identity, and the Global Multicultural War of All Against All", 1993-1994; 5.0 folders 5 folders (Box 41)
- "An Act of Imagination. Finding out that the Jews Were Not the Only Ones Who Had Undergone Genocide, Remembering the Armenian Genocide", undated (Box 41)
- "The Arena", undated (Box 41)
- "Joseph", undated (Box 41)
- "Oedipus" and "Wooden O" (fragment), Feb 1989 (Box 41)
- "Climbing a Crystal Staircase: Moses Sheldon Hall", undated (Box 41)
- "The Destiny Algorithm", Jan 16, 1994 (Box 41)
- "Some Theses on Power and Capital as a System of Power", undated (Box 41)
- "Euroiden/Commu-end version", Dec 17, 1993 (Box 41)
- "Within this Wooden O" (fragment), Feb 1, 1994 (Box 41)
- "Fausts stages of Spiritual/Economic Growth and Takeoff Into Transcendence" (fragments), undated (Box 41)
- Handwritten Notes, circa 1985 (Box 41)
- "Oedipus, or the Coup", 1993-1994; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 41)
- "Faust", undated (Box 41)
- Handwritten Notes and Outlines, undated (Box 41)
- "How the Athenians Plotted to Infiltrate and Colonize the Mind of the West and Immortalize Themselves", Mar 14, 1994-Mar 17, 1994 (Box 41)
- "Proposal for a Production to be Called Arena" By Yurick, Ronald, Dobson, Chip, and Quigley, undated (Box 41)
- "On the Deconstruction of the Jews", undated (Box 41)
- "Suite Vengeance: A Treatment" By Yurick, Dobson, and Quigley, undated (Box 41)
- "Burning", 1991-1992; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 41)
- "And, As We Once Again Begin Our Story Outline Here We Should Have an Overall Statement of the Novel", undated (Box 41)
- "Suicide", Feb 8, 1992-Mar 27, 1992 (Box 41)
- "On the Deconstruction of the Jews", 1995; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 42)
- Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 42)
- "The Sacrifice" By Sol Yurick and Ron Dobson, undated; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 42)
- "Burning", 1994; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 42)
- "Oediplay" (fragment), undated (Box 42)
- "Behold the Metatron, the Recording Angel", undated (Box 42)
- "Outline of Climbing a Crystal Staircase: The Moses Hall Story", undated (Box 42)
- "Poly-Oed" (fragment), undated (Box 42)
- "Jew decon", Sep 15, 1992-Feb 11, 1995 (Box 42)
- "The Emergence of the EuroAmerican Dominated Metastate versus the Politics of Identity", undated (Box 42)
- "Moses Hall", undated (Box 42)
- "Within this Wooden O", May 1989, Oct 1993 (Box 42)
- Fragments of Typescript drafts, undated (Box 42)
- "Bank Burning", Oct 1993-Jul 1994 (Box 42)
- "Samel's Sermon: A Tour of the Horizon", Sep 1994 (Box 42)
- "Oedipus, or The Coup", 1993-1994; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 42)
- "Euro-iden", Jan 1, 1980 (Box 42)
- "Burning the Bank of America", Apr 29, 1992-May 6, 1992 (Box 42)
- "Suicide" (and Oedipus notes), Feb 12, 1992, undated (Box 42)
- "Suicide", 1992; 4.0 folders 4 folders (Box 42)
- "The Destiny Algorithm", 1992; 2.0 folders 2 folders (Box 42)
- "Bereshit: Or the Great Escape", Oct 5, 1992-Nov 12, 1992 (Box 42)
- "Deconstruction of the Jews", Oct 2, 1992-Oct 6, 1992 (Box 42)
- Drew University- Interface with Sol Yurick (VHS recording), Jan 16, 1989; 1.0 videocassette (Box 43)
- "Moses Hall" (audio recording on Sony MC60 cassette), undated; 6.0 audiocassettes (Box 43)
- Bachelor of Arts Diploma New York University, 1951 (Box MSOS 006, Folder 1)